indianbluebook.com 2014-07-18

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
Mahindra First Choice Wheels Limited (The Company) takes your privacy seriously.
Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy
What this Privacy Policy Covers?
      This Privacy Policy covers the Company’s treatment of personally identifiable
       information that the Company collects when you are on the Company’s
       website, and when you use the Company's services. This policy also covers
       the Company's treatment of any personally identifiable information that the
       Company's business partner's share with the Company.
      This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Mahindra First
       Choice Wheels does not own or control, or to people that the Company does
       not employ or manage.
Information Collection and Use
      The Company collects personally identifiable information when you register
       for an www.indianbluebook.com account /membership
      When you register with the Company, we ask for your name, email address,
       birth date, gender, pin code, occupation, industry, and personal interests.
      The Company also automatically receives and records information on its
       server logs from your browser including your IP address.
      The Company uses information for two general purposes: To fulfil your
       requests for certain products and services and to contact you about the
       Company’s Online Marketplace.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
      The Company will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to
       anyone.
      The Company will send personally identifiable information about you to
       other companies or people when:
           o We have your consent to share the information;
           o We need to share your information to provide the product or service
              you have requested;
           o We need to share the information with certain service partners in
              order to respond to your comments or to resolve service issues.
              (Unless we tell you differently, these partners have no independent
              right to use this information except to respond to your comments or
              to resolve the service issues.)
           o We respond to requests from any Indian or foreign government,
              security, defence, revenue, regulatory or other authority, agency or
              officer;
           o We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
           o We find that your actions on our web sites violate the IBB User
              Agreement or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or
              services.
Security

     Your Membership Account Information is password-protected for your
      privacy and security.
     In certain areas the Company uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to
      protect data transmissions.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
     The Company may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any
      substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will
      notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our site.
Legal Requests
     We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties
      to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights fraud and other rights,
      to help protect you and the community from bad actors. Therefore, in
      response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government
      officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can
      (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number,
      email address, User ID history, fraud complaints, and car listing history
      without a subpoena or summon. Without limiting the above, in an effort to
      respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad
      actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law
      enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order
      or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith
      that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical
      harm or financial loss; or report suspected illegal activity. Further, we can
      (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, street address, city, state, zip
      code, country, phone number, email, and company name to intellectual
      property rights owners under confidentiality agreement, as we in our sole
      discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an
      investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other
      unlawful        activity.
      Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of
      your private communications and other personal information will never be
      disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of
      example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose
      personal information to the government or third parties under certain
      circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access
      transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse
      your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore,
      although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do
      not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or
      private communications will always remain private.
      Your Obligations
      You agree, undertake and confirm that while providing your information on
      the Site you will not host, display, upload, modify, publish, transmit, update
      or share any information that:-

(a) belongs to another person and to which you do not have any right to;
(b) is grossly harmful, harassing, blasphemous, defamatory, obscene,
pornographic, pedophilic, libelous, invasive of another privacy hateful, or racially,
ethnically objectionable, disparaging, relating or encouraging money laundering or
gambling, or otherwise unlawful in any manner whatever;
(c) harm minor in any way;
(d) infringes any patent, trademark, copyright or other proprietary rights;
(e) violates any law for the time being in force;
(f) deceives or misleads the Site and or existing and new users about the origin of
such messages or communicates any information which is grossly offensive or
menacing in nature;
(g) impersonate any other person;
(h) contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs
designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer resource;
or
(i) threatens the unity, integrity, defence, security or sovereignty of India, friendly
relations with foreign states, or public order or causes incitement to the
commission of any cognizable offence or prevents investigation of any offence or is
insulting any other nation.
